Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
?1
Do you know how
wrong it is to have a daughter
and simply choose not to
speak to her for eight years?
You think I wanted any of this to happen?
Grow some balls and go down
there and see your little girl.
Hey.
- I'm your father.
- It doesn't change the fact
that you walked out on your nine kids.
You had nine kids?
Seven. The twins weren't born yet.
- What's eating at you?
- I wouldn't tell you.
Oh, okay.
- Go throw with the guy.
- What? Why?
Come on. You'll get along great together.
Seems to me like you've lost somebody...
Somebody you had feelings for.
You're good at what you do, Loudermilk.
Mm.
Think she bought it?
Meatballs are ready.
You paid this little asshole to talk to me.
- Nah.
- You tricked me again!
If it ain't broke...
I love that one, too.
It's called "Oil and Water."
'Cause that's a bag of oil
and that's a bag of water.
Neat.
There's an ironic sense of whimsy
in all of Shoreline's work.
This one explores the duality of conflict
that resides within the human psyche.
Don't you love when art does that?
Mm.
Unfortunately, this
piece has been purchased.
That is unfortunate...
for whoever bought it.
Honestly, I'd rather have
shit and piss on my wall.
Come on, man. Enough with the snark.
You're ruining it for everyone.
No. I mean, right over there.
"Shit and Piss."
For the dining room, no?
Honey, let's get the fuck out of here.
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.MY-SUBS.com
All right, so, I told you
guys about my old band, right?
No.
You managed a band?
No, I was in a band.
Back in the '90s.
What, uh, instrument did you play?
Drums.
Seriously, what instrument?
Really, I was the drummer.
What did you need, like,
extra-long sticks or something?
Hey, uh, quit breaking his balls.
No, I'm not breaking his balls.
I would think that you'd
need extra-long sticks,
'cause of the T. rex thing.
I just used regular,
18-inch, standard sticks.
What kind of music did you play?
Oh, real rock 'n' roll.
Back in '96, we toured on a triple bill
with Dokken and Skid Row.
- Wow.
- We charted once.
- You guys had a hit?
- Mm-hmm.
- What was it called?
- "Boilerbreaker."
Well, isn't that Sauced Puppy?
Yeah.
You were in Sauced Puppy?
Wow!
You guys sucked.
No, no, no. I liked that song.
? Boilerbreaker ?
- Oh, God.
- ? Boilerbreaker ?
What's a boilerbreaker?
It's a modified boilermaker.
Our lead singer invented it.
You drop a double shot of
whiskey into a pint of beer.
So good.
So... so, tell us about
the groupies there, Roger.
You ever get one of them double blowjobs?
- You know, like, two dicks, one mouth?
- Heh.
Oh, my God. Check this out.
Okay. Can we let Roger
finish his share, please?
So, a couple of weeks ago,
our bass player called me,
and apparently, Sweeny's
Ale wants to use the band
in one of their commercials.
That's fucking awesome.
Well, back in the day,
it would've been awesome.
But where I am now in life,
I don't want to promote booze.
It's just beer.
Well, it's not just beer, though.
Brother Jay's Whiskey, and
now 'Cause Sweeny's bought out
they're making a drink that's
beer and whiskey combined.
Hey, Roger, why don't you
just let them use the song?
Who gives a fuck?
Guys, guys.
This is exactly the point
that I was trying to make earlier, okay?
You all have to make decisions
that are gonna make you
feel good about yourself.
So you think I'm doing the right thing
Turning down the 100 grand?
Absolutely...
How much?
100 grand.
Per guy.
For fucking "Boilerbreaker"?
Well, come on, man. Be straight with me.
What should I do?
Look, whatever you think, okay?
If you think you should
pass, you should pass.
Maybe you could come with me,
Help me explain it to the guys in the band.
Fuck, no.
Why should I be the one to tell them?
You're the one screwing them over.
But you just said it was
the right thing to do.
Yeah, well, it probably is, but, you know,
the thing about doing the right thing
is it usually pisses somebody off.
Come on, Loudermilk, please.
I really could use some help.
All right, let's, uh,
let's wrap this up, m'kay?
Good meeting, everybody.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. Look, I like your daughter,
But you gotta get her off my couch.
Why? Is everything okay?
Did she relapse?
No, she's fine. She's doing fine.
Well, if she's doing fine,
Then we should stick with what's working.
No need to rock the boat, right?
No, no.
We need to rock the boat
until she falls off the boat
and swims to a couch on her own boat, okay?
I was happy to help her out,
but I got a life to get back to.
Not that I've seen.
What if I give you a thank-you gift
to show my appreciation?
Could she stay a little longer?
Wait! You're going to bribe him?
Stay out of this!
What'd you have in mind?
Well...
I could give you my husband's car.
It's just collecting
dust in the garage anyway.
He can't accept gifts over $25.
Says who? You're just making shit up now.
You're a drug-and-alcohol counselor.
Taking expensive gifts
from your group members
Or from their families is unethical.
It's the same for me as a man of the cloth.
Bullshit!
Like you paid for this place?
And what about the pope?
He's got a... custom-designed super Hummer.
You don't even have a license.
What would you do with a car?
He can sell it, for all I care.
I can sell it, for all she cares.
Yeah, I'll take the car.
And Claire can continue to stay with you?
Forgot there was a catch.
Yeah. For now.
I'll have someone bring
the vehicle by tomorrow.
Awesome.
Hey.
Hey!
What you watchin'?
It's, uh, "White Zombie."
Yeah, it's like "Walking
Dead," but really boring.
It's terrible. Sit down.
Tempting, but I think I'm
gonna go try and get some Z's
before snore-a-saurus
starts rattling the I-beams.
Look, I know I snore,
but it's like a sweet
little ladylike snore.
It's like a silverback fucking
a badger without its consent.
Okay, well, I slept
next to Wyatt for months,
and he didn't say a word.
He was on heroin.
He'd have slept through a kidney stone.
Okay, well, Ben hasn't said a word.
Well, I've always been a super sleeper...
Since I was a kid.
You're not a kid, so don't
say "super sleeper" again.
I think you have a medical condition, okay?
Oh, God.
I think you need one of those
machines that helps you breathe,
like Darth Vader has.
A CPAP. My dad had one.
Really? I'm that bad?
Yeah, you stop breathing for minutes.
It's like David Blaine-level shit.
I don't know how you
don't have brain damage.
Maybe I do.
Hey, I saw my mom's car in the parking lot.
What, was she checking up on me?
Well, you know, I think, in her mind,
you're on your own now.
Well, what'd she say?
Well, she's glad to hear you're doing well,
and she gave me your father's car.
What? Wait... Are you serious?
She gave you my dad's
Escalade? The car he died in?
What did you say?
Yeah, my dad died in that car.
No, no, no. The part... the part...
D-Did you say "Escalade"?
That's like a $90,000 truck.
Yeah, it's like $110,000 with
all the features he added.
No. No, no.
Your mom's not gonna give
me a brand-new Escalade.
What other cars did your dad have?
Uh, that's it.
I mean, she sold the Lincoln a while back.
That's the only car.
Actually perfect for you.
The new Escalades
practically drive themselves.
It's like KITT from "Knight Rider."
You won't even need a license.
Uh, yeah, you will need a license.
Oh, I won't need a license.
I'm not gonna drive it.
Probably just sell it.
What?!
You're gonna profit off
the car my dad died in?
He died in it?
I just told you that a minute ago!
No, you didn't.
What?! D... D...
Ben.
Uh... ah...
Pretty sure I would've remembered
you saying something like that.
You gonna let me drive
it before you sell it?
Yeah, if I get to ride shotgun.
Holy shit.
Um, I'm gonna try and get down
before the, you know, lumber
mill starts with the...
...lumber milling.
You're out of toilet paper again.
Again?
It's like you're single-handedly
clear-cutting the rainforest
with your asshole.
Oh, fuck off.
Hey, how was my snoring last night?
Awful. Terrible. Worse.
Well, I guess you'll just
have to start sleeping
in your fancy new car.
Yeah, or you have to get
one of those CPAP things.
Um, I would, but you need a prescription.
And when I was in boarding school,
no one would room with
me, so I looked into it.
Oh! So you know you have a problem.
Yeah, I do.
But... I don't know...
When I started doing coke,
I thought it went away.
Nope. Didn't go away.
Okay. Well...
Look, I'd go to the doctor,
but I don't have insurance,
so...
Sorry.
Hey. Sorry to bother you, but, uh,
I'm... fresh out of sugar.
Well, what do you need? Like,
a gram? An eight ball? Or...
Uh, is your Dr. McDreamy here?
No, he doesn't like to
stay over when he's on call.
He hates waking me up.
Okay.
Chivalrous.
He seems like an interesting guy.
I'd like to meet him.
You met him the other night.
Well, for two seconds.
I'd like to get to know
him, though, you know?
Uh...
We should all grab a meal sometime.
I'm meeting him at lunch today at Marty's.
Do you want to join us?
Yeah. That'll work.
Okay. Well, here you go.
Ah.
Better not be stepping on this shit, huh?
This thing drives like a dream.
It's pretty fucking sweet, right?
Man. Smell the leather.
I think this is what Dubai smells like.
It's an impressive gift.
Yeah. You should check out the
bowling alley I got in back.
Seriously, the Blue Book
value on this thing is insane.
This is the place.
We're meeting them at a car wash?
Yeah. They work there.
What's up? Billy.
Holy shit!
Roger-Dodger!
Is this your car?
No. No, it's his.
Hi. It's my car.
- Hey.
Hey, um, thanks for coming down
to talk this out face-to-face.
I know things got a little
heated on the text thread.
No problem.
Where's Maggie?
Uh, he's right over there.
Yo! Mags!
Hey.
Who's this fuck?
You lawyer up on us?
No. This is Loudermilk. He's a friend.
Pleasure.
Hey.
All right, then.
- Should we, uh, talk business?
- Yeah.
Not here. We're supposed to be working.
Pull inside.
Oh. Okay.
Make sure it's in neutral.
Yeah, okay.
Okay. Bring out the contract.
Show him where to sign.
I already told you guys.
I'm not gonna sign that.
I came here today as a courtesy
to you both to explain why.
D-Do you know what?
- Oh, Christ!
- Mags, what are you doing?
I'm getting this guy to
sign the fucking papers
one way or another.
Dude, relax, all right? Nobody nee...
The fuck kinda gun is that?
You got a problem with it?!
No. No, no. Hey, look.
I'm not here for a musket
ball to the head, all right?
I'm just supporting my friend Roger.
This is just like Wichita all over again.
You didn't shoot then, and
you're not gonna shoot now.
Don't tempt me, Roger.
My life is shit right now, and
I have nothing to lose, okay?
And I'm really sorry about that,
but I'm still not gonna sign.
Are we sure this is not gonna
scratch the finish? 'Cause...
Help me understand where
your head's at here, Roger.
I mean, what is wrong with us
making a little bit of money off our art?
They want our song to
promote binge drinking
and having sex with passed-out women.
Blacked-out women!
It's a big difference.
What? What is the difference?
How are we gonna know if
they're blacked out, Roger?!
They're walking and
talking Like everyone else!
Yeah!
Put the fucking gun down, Maggie.
Just...
Oh, for fuck's sake!
Come on, Roger!
Please?!
This commercial could
get me back on my feet...
maybe open a little pizza joint.
The residuals alone will
get me off my cousin's couch.
You get residuals?
Fuck, yeah!
It'll double what we get paid.
We could make 200 grand... Each!
That's a lot of money, Roger.
I know.
But it doesn't matter.
Dude, you're the real deal, you know?
I mean, you may die broke,
but you're rich with integrity.
Shut the fuck up, you fucking hypocrite!
Driving up in here with
your fancy fucking Esplanade,
telling Roger to turn
down money that he needs!
Roger...
Ow! Fuck.
Don't listen to this dick!
Listen to your friends.
You could have your own Esplanade.
All right, first off, it's a
fucking Escalade, all right?
And I didn't do anything
for this. It was a gift.
Hey, you're the one who's always going on
saying no gift comes
without strings attached...
Except the gift you give yourself.
I didn't say that. You saw that
on a cat calendar or something.
Nobody's perfect, Rog.
Come on.
Just... bend...
a little.
Fuck it!
And so when I got the residency,
I asked Allie to move to Seattle,
And, lucky for me, she said yes.
And, lucky for me, I
was able to find a sublet
in your apartment building on short notice.
Yeah, I wouldn't call anyone
lucky in that building.
It's like...
a big pile of asbestos held
together with lead paint.
So, what about work? What'd they say?
Well, they weren't very
happy, but, luckily,
Sotheby's has offices everywhere, so...
So it all worked out.
Yeah.
Aw.
So, how come you two don't
actually live together?
Oh, you know, um... my hours
are so unpredictable, so...
Well, and... and we
practically do live together.
It's just like he said...
With the crazy timing
and me and my new job.
- Right.
- It... it just...
Right. Right, right, right, right, right.
So, hey, Dr. Carl...
uh... I'm sure you hate it
when people ask you
for free medical advice,
but this isn't about me.
It's about the dirty little drug fiend
who's sleeping on my couch.
Okay, um... What's the problem?
She's got this, uh,
deviated-septum, sleep-apnea,
possible demon-living-in-
the-throat situation,
and the snoring is just...
it's nuts.
I think she could really use
one of those CPAP machines.
'Cause those work, right?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, but she should see a doctor,
find out what's causing the problem.
Well, I got a doctor
sitting right across from me.
Yeah, a sleep specialist.
Yeah, that's not a real thing.
Here. Listen. This is her.
I made this recording
last night, okay? Listen.
Wow.
Yeah? Listen to this.
She quits breathing for
2 minutes and 36 seconds.
All right? Another time,
it's closer to four minutes,
but I-I-I just didn't have
the phone handy to document it.
Well, I can see why that would worry you.
Oh, I'm not worried. I just
want to get some sleep at night.
I need to use the ladies' room.
Yeah. Sure.
Look, I can't just grab you a CPAP machine.
That's not how it works. There
are rules and regulations.
Come on, you gotta have,
like, a crappy old used one
Laying around somewhere, right?
Missing some knobs or it's a little moldy.
Yeah?
I think that guy's choking.
Uh...
Dr. Carl!
Hey...
Fuck's sake.
Guhh!
Dude, you... You gotta remember to chew.
What happened?
This guy just saved my life.
He was choking.
Oh, honey.
Not him.
Him.
What? Loudermilk?
Hey, how is that? I almost ordered that.
It's...
- ...fine. Fine. Yeah.
- No? All right.
Look, the guy had it under control, okay?
He didn't need my help.
Nobody's saying otherwise.
Well, you're both sitting there judging me
for not doing anything. I can feel it.
Thing is, I was doing something.
I was assessing the situation,
waiting to see if I was needed.
- Really?
-The guy was working it out on his own.
Yeah. Maybe.
Nope... definitely.
No... maybe.
By way of "probably not."
Will you stop it? The guy was fine.
How come his face was turning blue?
It wasn't turning blue.
It was flush... From coughing.
He didn't cough.
He couldn't cough. He grunted.
Cough...
Grunt...
- It's a big difference.
- Right.
Look, guys, the guy is fine.
That's all that matters.
Yeah, why don't you stop
trying to be a hero, Loudermilk?
Hey, I'm not a hero.
I just did what anyone
would do in that situation.
Right, except me.
The only one in the room who
studied medicine for seven years
and knows exactly how to
react in that situation.
Carl, come on. Just admit
it. You fucking choked, okay?
He choked, and then you choked.
It's all right. Nobody's perfect.
I work in an ER. I don't choke.
I have ice water in my veins.
Well, I'm sure you do...
In the safe confines of the operating room,
where there's a whole bunch of
other doctors and nurses around
when something goes wrong.
Look... Okay.
There's other factors to
consider here, Loudermilk, okay?
Doctors have to be very
cautious when administering aid.
We can get sued.
- O... kay.
- Happens all the time.
Let's just drop it.
I didn't bring it up. He did.
Hi. Excuse me. Hi. Can I get the check?
No need for that. Your meal's
been comped by management.
It's the least we could do.
Oh.
Great.
That's very generous.
You get the tip.
It goes to 5, but never
turn a CPAP up to 5.
My dad did that once... He
blew up to twice his size.
He was floating around
the room. It was awful.
My mom woke up in the morning,
and she had to hit him with,
like, a needle to pop him,
and then at breakfast, he
farted for eight minutes.
Holy shit. Is that what I think it is?
Yeah, it's a CPAP, and
Carl brought it over.
Pretty nice of the good
doctor, don't you think?
No, I think he just did
it 'cause he felt guilty.
Uh, why? Because he's sleeping
with your imaginary girlfriend?
No, we were having lunch,
and some guy started choking.
Okay, and Dr. Carl just
sits there looking at him
like he's a turd on a log.
Wait... So what happened?
Yeah, did the fucking guy die?
No, no, he didn't die, but only because
I had to jump up and save him, you know?
Like, I've got a doctor
sitting right across from me.
I've never even taken the
damn class, and here I am...
I get up and I'm giving
him the Heimlich maneuver.
So I guess he got Heimlock.
You just make that up?
Yeah, it's when you're gonna
give the Heimlich Maneuver,
but then you freeze up, so it's Heimlock.
No? All right, well, they
can't all be slam dunks.
I'm starting to think Dr.
Carl's not even a real doctor.
Oh, what are you even complaining for?
You got to look like a hero
in front of your lady friend
And then we got a CPAP machine.
It's true.
- That goes in your nose.
- I know.
Do I look sexy?
If I'm an elephant.
Wait... Are you saying I'm fat?
- No, he's talking about your ears.
- Hey.
I feel like a fucking moron in this getup.
No, y-you look like Andre Agassi.
You need anything?
Yeah, can you grab me a Coke?
I've got to drink something.
You got it.
Are you an idiot? How could
you not know about this?
They never had a video. How would I know?
Jesus Christ.
How does he even play the drums?
I... With his feet, maybe?
This is fucked up.
We have to replace this guy ASAP.
He's a poster child for
fetal alcohol syndrome.
I mean, what's our messaging here...
If you drink Sweeny's, you become deformed?
- Is that our messaging?
- Okay, okay, okay.
What am I supposed to do?
Just get rid of him!
All right.
Hey. Roger, come here.
Listen...
how bad do you want this thing?
What do you mean?
This commercial.
I don't want it at all.
But I can't let them down.
Why? He fucking pulled a gun on you.
That's just Maggie.
Forget him. Just...
If you don't want to
do it, man, don't do it.
Period. End of story.
If it's not what you're all about...
I mean, I get it... It's a big paycheck.
I get that, okay?
I got an Escalade somebody handed me,
and I probably shouldn't keep that.
I definitely shouldn't keep that.
'Cause it makes me a sellout.
Understand?
Do I want to be a sellout
for an awesome, tricked-out, luxury SUV?
Hey, Rog? Can I get a
word with you, please?
Not now. We're gonna
do a quick sound check.
Just the first verse.
Sound check, everybody! Let's go!
Sound check!
One, two, three, four!
? Boilerbreaker, boilerbreaker ?
? Take it all in ?
? It's only time till you make her ?
? Body's built for sin ?
Owwwww!
Are you fucking shitting me?
This guy's incredible!
This shit could go viral.
Yeah!
Boom!
Oh, that was some wicked shit, my man!
Let's get out of here.
Yeah?
To take the car for one
last high-speed drive
before you give it back.
Did I say I was giving it back?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Rog! Where you going?
Sorry, guys.
- I'm done.
- What?
He's out. He's not doing your commercial.
Hey, we have a contract!
Fuck you!
Hey. What's this still doing here?
I thought you said you
were gonna give it back.
I did give it back.
Boys.
Are you fucking kidding me?
She gave this to you?
Yep.
What about all that shit about
you don't take expensive gifts?
Well, you remember your
pope/Hummer argument?
Well, it carried a lot of weight with me.
I was told I could find
a Sam Loudermilk here?
Yeah, that's me.
Meeting's in there. It
starts in 10 minutes.
I'm not here for a meeting.
- You're being sued.
- For what?
For breaking my client's ribs
while recklessly administering
The Heimlich maneuver
when it wasn't needed.
Motherfucker.
You know, if you hadn't taken
that, you couldn't get sued.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm just trying to help.